<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Interweb World</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Interweb World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building A Site With Hugo, Github and Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/05/building-a-site-with-hugo-github-and-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/05/building-a-site-with-hugo-github-and-netlify/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The hot new thing in web development is actually pretty old: static websites. But these are static sites with a twist: using modern web development tools to build and deploy a complete website.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing a lot about Hugo these days - a superfast static site generator. Static has a lot of advantages: you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about resource-hungy server-side technologies such as PHP or MySQL. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about Content Management Systems, frequent patching and security updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>